This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Maki D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy fell captive to the strange net-net powers of Largo,
the captain of the Amigo Pirate.
While I admire your elastic nature, I'm afraid you must pay your comeuppance, senor.
But Largo's true target was the giant beetle, Boss,
who surrendered himself in an attempt to save his home from the pirates.
Hold on!
I know you can hear me!
Boss then shed his skin, destroying the nets holding Luffy and his friends.
This is awful. It must have been too soon for him to mold.
Your screaming and crying won't do any good.
Good. No one's gonna save you winding peasants now that we got your guardian angel.
The fight's not over yet.
Okay?
You didn't risk your life for nothing.
We'll save your friends, Boss.
We owe you that much. You give everything to us.
Well, the fun's over. It's time to get serious.
A special presentation related to the movie. The battle is on. Luffy vs. Largo.
You're joking! You need me to spell out the odds for you?
Three burned men and a handful of weak sea cowards with shovels and rakes.
Do you really think you're gonna take the beetle back from us now?
That's right.
Now fork over Boss!
Or else!
We want it back!
Thank you.
Come on, let's see what you punks have got.
Zoro, cut the net open.
Sure.
Did the beetle burn out your short-term memory?
No matter how sharp your blades may be, they're still not strong enough to cut through my nets.
Don't speak so soon.
Wait for it. Lion Strike!
We're a part of this fight too!
Don't be stupid!
Huh?
Alright, second gear!
Sanchi!
I need a boost, you know where I'm going!
You got it.
Okay, net man, you're going down!
Am I?
Such confidence!
Armaid's lair!
Assault gum!
Shoot!
Jet bullet!
You guys take care of the rest!
No problem!
Did he take out Big Bro that easy?
No, he just caught him off guard.
Largo's sure to beat that little punk.
At least he better if he wants us to get in with Big Bo Shiki!
That hurt enough for you or you want some more?
Well, that jogged my memory.
I know that hat of yours.
You have a 300 million berry bounty.
You are Monkey Diluffi, see?
Yeah, that's me.
It's a tragedy to end one's life at such a young age.
But I couldn't lament your lost life compared to the loss of such a bounty.
Mucho burning net!
Gum gum! Jet plant!
Ah!
Mucho sticky net!
This is no bueno.
I need to find some open terrain to fight him on.
He's running!
Your backup's gone.
Not surprising since they're from the East Blue.
Guess the rumors are true.
They don't call it the weak sea for nothing.
No.
They took off because it was obvious that we didn't need any backup.
They knew two East Blue natives are more than enough.
Slow down! Stop running!
Take us back! We were about to kick their pirate butts!
You sound like a damn fool!
You can't just confront them head on like that!
It's suicide!
Exactly!
You can't fight them on their own terms.
You've got to work with your strengths if you want to win.
Which means outsmarting them!
Come on! We need to hurry!
Hey!
Don't tell me what to do, you dumb pirate!
Listen kid, do you want them to destroy the island and take the beetle?
You've got to trust me if you don't want them to win.
I don't want them to win.
Do you promise?
If I trust you and go along with your plan, do you promise me I'll get boss back?
Yeah.
So, are you ready?
Hmph.
Well, let's do it!
Yeah!
You really think the two of you are enough?
Your dilutions are as big as your mouth!
They outnumber us, but that's all they've got.
If you're scared, you can always sit this one out.
First, I'm going to kick their asses, and then I'm going to kick yours.
All right, you guys!
Let's!
Get those bastards!
Die!
What the hell?
You mess with us and you die!
Run, you cowards!
We don't want you here!
Where did they come from?
Save that!
Surprised to see us?
There's a giant network of caves hidden inside the mountain back there.
And they open up to all the different parts of the island.
Using it as an escape route felt like kind of a waste.
So I thought we could stage a little surprise ambush.
Take cover, guys! We've got a storm coming!
Now, Thunderbolt!
Tempo!
No!
Okay, this is getting bad.
Let's attack while they're still down!
Jet!
How the hell is this happening?
Huh?
Special attack, Eggstar!
Grossy, stinky!
Nicely done!
Ah!
They're awesome!
No one makes a fool out of me!
Comprende!
What the?
I don't know what to think here.
I'll kill every last one of you!
No!
Huh?
Bug?
Die, you damn bug!
Out of ammo?
What have you done to me, hermano?
As a requiem for my beloved kin.
I'll kill your crew.
Captain first!
Now that we've traded the confines of the jungle for open spaces, you'll surely perish!
Oh yeah?
I'm pretty sure I can kick your ass anywhere!
Bring it!
Your blood with arrogance!
Show me your best, senor!
Ah!
Hm?
What's that all about?
It's filthy!
He seems to be engaged in battle.
Jet!
Ha-zah!
No shock!
Net body!
What's that?
I hate to tell you, but you can't hurt me now!
He-he-he!
Dom-Dom-Jet!
Tell me!
It's not worth it!
How long do you plan to keep it up?
How long till I knock you on your ass?!
This guy must have a devil fruit power!
He's not getting hurt!
Well that can't be good.
No!
Quit prolonging the inevitable!
For me, hermano!
I will make your death cry his funeral day!
Mucho, mucho!
Full Net Body!
Lupin, no!
What happened?
There is no escape from retribution now!
Struggle all you like, but you will never break this net!
What the what?
Looks like a submersible vessel of some sort.
Wait, don't tell me they're using it as a pirate ship!
So it would seem.
How sweet it will be when I trade in your corpse for 300 million berries!
Third gear!
Huh?
Bone Balloon!
Hey!
What's that?
Ah!
Please stop!
GANF!
GUM GUM!
Bryant...
...pictop!
So you are more realistic than you.
Book!
You don't!
Yikes.
Give me the boy!
I'm coming to your rescue, Levine!
I gotcha!
Oh, I forgot that I'm unable to swim.
I feared I was slipping over the brink of dash.
So in my case, the implications of that are rather vague.
Thanks, big guy. I owe you one.
Oh, jeez! What was that for?
You cheater! You could barely shoot fire a few minutes ago!
All right, that's it! Our fight starts right now!
I would appreciate it if you'd put me down first.
Hurry!
Whoa!
They're still going.
I'm starting to think this fight will never end.
Yeah.
Okay, round three!
Miss you, Dad.
Hey, there you are.
Mind if I sit?
What are you doing here?
I heard there was an orange plantation.
Thought I'd check it out.
What an incredible view.
You know, my dad used to come out here all the time.
We both did.
Isn't the view just lovely?
There's simply no place in the world I like better than this one.
Yeah!
It's so pretty!
I love it up here!
I really, really, really love it!
Well, I believe it.
Let's burn it down!
Gather up any food and valuables who can kill anyone who tries to get in our way!
Dad!
Wake up!
Yoko.
Hurry.
You must leave the island.
No way!
I can't!
I love it here too much to go!
If I leave, I'll never be able to visit my favorite place in the world again!
It's your favorite place too, remember?
With all the orange trees!
You're right, Yoko.
From now on...
It's your island.
No!
Dad!
Protect your home.
Be strong.
And brave.
We're a lot alike.
Huh?
I used to hate pirates just as much as you.
Yeah?
But then why did you become one?
Well...
It's kind of hard to explain.
Because her aunty title is spoiling me.
We're, it's really a classical Quite Canny.
Dear Queen,
Let's move!
Time to combine his owndies.
I mentioned hisと。
After all of a sudden drama will grant the
Nami! Just remember, you'll always be my friend!
You know, Luffy's not the kind of pirate you think. Not in the slightest.
Huh?
Listen! I'll come back tomorrow and we'll try again!
Shut up! Shut up! I don't give a damn about that!
All I want is to fuck that giant beetle!
Is that it?
Yeah, I think I see what you mean.
You do?
I get the feeling he's a little too dumb and goofy to be one of the bad pirates.
Exactly!
I got quiet all of a sudden. Did they finally finish their fight?
Guess so.
Well, let's see how Boss did.
So, you give up?
No!
He said no way. And he said that he won, too.
What?!
All right, break it up! It's time for us to head back out to sea!
Ugh! You can't be serious, Nami! We've got ten rounds left at least!
Come on! It only takes half of a day for this island's log to reset.
So we'd better take off unless we want to get stranded.
Ugh!
Farewell, Dummy!
Dummy!
Go!
I'm going to be coming back here some day.
We're picking up where we left off.
The fight's not over yet!
I thought these Amigo Pirates claimed to be specialists in trapping.
Maybe they are, but we've lost contact with them so we can only assume the worst.
Oh well, on the bright side at least we have some added reassurance that the monsters you
created are apt to snuff.
If I can live without one giant beetle, it won't affect my plans.
After all, I have plenty more bloodthirsty beasties to do my bidding in its absence.
We'll declare war against the whole damn world!
No one can stop me!
The good lion will reign supreme!
Jinn!
Sulfi and his Unlikely Companions defeat the Basilisk in a race through Level 2, only to encounter
even more ferocious beasts.
Meanwhile Ace finds himself with an unlikely companion as well when he exchanges words with
a powerful pirate prisoner.
On the next One Piece, the warlord in prison, Jinbei the honorable pirate, I will be king of the pirates!